LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
I'm a soldier - that means I'm
Both a defendant and the judge
I am standing on both ends of the flame
Rounding curves
Overtaking life and death,
I run and fight with false shadows
No matter how many threads of deception are woven together,
The truth shall illuminate the face of light
Save your tears for the day
when our pain is far behind
on your feet, come with me
We are soldiers stand or die
Save your fears, take your place
Save them for the judgement day
fast and free, follow me
Time to make the sacrifice.
We rise or fall
Is she going to the restroom?
Looks that way.
Shall we follow her?
Well, wait a second.
The restroom's floor and walls are tiled.
The window is fixed and has an
aluminium grid on the outside.
While I think she'd be easily
capable of breaking through that,
I doubt she'd do anything so crude.
Kusa Meikyu
Grass Labyrinth
Note: This is the title of a 1979 film by Terayama Shuji
and a pun on Kusanagi
God, it's hot...
Here, a present.
Er, beer... ?
Damn, you're lucky.
You people get to break down
alcohol with internal implants.
Anyway, isn't the difficulty level for the
Section 9 recruitment test set wrong?
Don't be an idiot.
If they can't pass something this easy, it
means the quality of these candidates is low, right?
Well, yeah, but...
Batou.
What?
What's going on?
Reading a newspaper and drinking some coffee.
Not you; I'm asking about them.
Well, that's who I'm talking about.
They're all relaxed.
I wonder if they're incapable of considering the
possibility that they may have been fed a false memory.
I taught them that right off the bat.
How many are left?
Three pairs, six agents.
Let's go on to the next pair.
Roger that.
Is this the last pair?
Yeah, unfortunately.
Water Bus
We're sorry, but we've lost the target!
Ah. What're you going to do about it?
We'll try sweeping the area one more time, but...
Oh, okay.
Do your best, then.
Aren't you being a bit cold?
What's the point of feeling sorry for them?
Major, we're done.
Let's go home.
Major?
I'm not connecting.
I wonder if she got mad and went home already...
A hacking?
Batou.
Batou!
So it is a hack...
I didn't sense anyone getting past my quad-layer firewall...
If this is by a trainee, it's pretty impressive.
Memorabilia Store
So, this is the goal.
OPEN
What is this feeling?
What the touch receptors of my skin feel is clearly real...
yet... the whole experience is surreal.
Cybernetic bodies...?
Aren't they adorable? Those children.
Are you the shopkeeper?
Something like that, yes.
What is it that you'd like to entrust to this store?
Entrust?
Indeed.
This is a shop that takes in customers' external memories.
What we have in this store has no value
whatsoever from another person's point of view,
but each item has a lot of its
former owner's memories packed into it.
Because of that, I sometimes feel
breathless from all the residual thoughts they give off.
Residual thoughts...?
Weren't you also attracted here by them?
These are very rare models that were made
when full-body cyborgs were still in their early stages.
The memories associated with
these children always sadden me.
However, at the same time, it allows me to appreciate
the joy of receiving the memories of others for safekeeping.
What type of memory is
associated with these children?
Goodness gracious, it's already this late.
I'm very sorry, but we're closing early today.
Please come by again when you have time.
I'll take my time to tell you the story.
I see...
That strange sensation was...
Hey man, let's go home already.
We'll report to the Major tomorrow.
Major, it was really uncool of you to disappear like that.
Where have you been?
Oh, doing stuff...
So, how many recruits do you think will actually be hired?
Well, there's one guy from the GSDF Intelligence division
with a recommendation from
someone the Chief knows.
How un-reassuring.
I can't deny the fact that the
quality of our candidates is low,
but it's also a fact that acquiring reserve
personnel has been given high priority.
If we lower the difficulty level any further, though,
it just means our resources will be diluted.
So then what?
Further testing at a later date, I guess?
I'll decide after discussing it with the Chief.
Hey, do you really think I'm
suited to be a training supervisor?
If you weren't, no one else would be.
I'll be signing out early today.
Take care of the rest, thanks.
Don't worry about it.
Before joining Section 9, the Major
would have lost me in five minutes too.
Really?
Jeez, you suck.
What?
So you're saying you could tail
a target like the Major
who can vanish in the blink of an eye - all the way to the end?
Of course.
A daydream?
It could have been something more "spiritual"...
When I turn over in my sleep,
I sometimes have an out of body
experience and see strange things, but...
I see.
Then, have you ever felt that your possessions have thoughts?
Let's see...
On long drives, I've felt as though the car
was an extension of my arms and legs, but...
Oh, why don't we call Kuru-tan
and go partying for a change?
I'll pass.
I have something I need to take care of today.
The Major... what is she doing wandering
around yesterday's test course?
Did she spot me?
I was waiting for you.
I thought you'd be coming soon.
Why?
These children were anxious for you to come, after all.
I see.
Then please tell me about them, about those children.
How impatient you are.
Very well.
These two cybernetic bodies were
being carefully preserved by the boy,
who is now a full adult.
When that boy was six, he was in an airplane accident.
It was apparently a huge accident in
which most of the plane's passengers died,
and I heard that almost all of the
initial survivors passed away...
except this boy, and the girl, who
coincidentally sat next to him on the plane.
The two miraculously survived,
but the girl did not regain consciousness,
and the boy became completely
paralysed, save for his left arm.
After his injuries healed, the boy immediately
understood the situation he was in,
such as the fact that his parents,
who were also on the plane, were dead,
and the reason why his distant relatives, who at
first came to visit him and were caring towards him,
stopped coming all too soon...
He tried to accept all this as best
as he could with his still young mind,
and began to think of the girl,
who remained asleep in the bed next to his
and was in the same situation as him,
as his only friend in the entire world.
"Please, let her wake up..."
Note: In Japan it is said that a wish will come true if you make one thousand origami cranes
Praying for this to happen,
he continued to fold origami cranes,
using his left hand as best as he could.
However...
Did something happen to the girl?
After a while, the girl's condition suddenly changed.
Blood pressure: 60 over nothing!
Administer one unit each of
lidocaine and epinephrine!
I can't get an ECG on her.
Her blood pressure's down to 40.
Prepare the OR right away!
The next morning, the boy was told that
the girl had gone somewhere far away,
Over the next two years
the boy spoke to no one and continued
to fold cranes in silence...
as if continuing to fold those cranes was
a serious duty that had been cast upon him.
Has he said anything today?
Just "I want some white origami"...
One day, after all the paperwork from
the crash litigation was complete,
a young physician came to visit
with one of the boy's relatives,
and asked him,
"If you wish it, there is a treatment you can have that'll
repair all the parts of your body that won't move.
Do you have the courage to undergo this treatment?"
"If this all goes well, you'll be able to
lead a normal life, like you did before."
The boy didn't respond.
It's not that he couldn't summon
enough courage, or anything like that.
I wonder if you understand.
He had no motivation to want to return
to the normal life he had led before.
After all, he had no interest in doing
anything anymore, aside from folding cranes.
So the adults gave up trying to persuade him.
But one girl opened a window into the boy's heart.
And that was this girl?
Yes.
This girl had already undergone successful
treatment to change into a fully cybernetic body.
The young physician probably brought the two of them
together in a final attempt to persuade the boy.
The girl came every day to see the
boy, or so the story goes.
She was a very cheerful, active girl.
She must have experienced a lot of
difficulty before becoming a full cyborg,
but she didn't speak a single
word about it to the boy.
In contrast, she would periodically
encourage him to get cybernetic implants.
The boy would listen in silence,
but one day, he asked,
"Can you fold a crane using your cybernetic body?"
"If you can, I won't mind becoming a full cyborg."
However...
Even though she could make
her body exert force,
she wasn't able to command it to
carry out delicate movements just yet.
I wonder if the girl didn't like being defeated.
I heard she tried very hard to fold a crane.
The girl must have been a source of hope for the boy, too.
But see, they were still both very young.
The boy was crestfallen,
and said that if he couldn't continue to fold
cranes for the girl who had passed away,
he'd be just fine the way he was.
After that day, the girl never
appeared before the boy again,
leaving behind the words, "This time, I'll
practice folding cranes for you, okay?"
Yes, she was the girl whom the
boy had believed to have died.
Why did she not tell him?
I'm sure there was a very serious reason for that...
but that day, the boy made a
decision to get cybernetic implants
and vowed to go meet the girl,
who disappeared from the hospital.
Later on, the boy became a full cyborg,
and withstood a difficult rehabilitation
to become a very skilled user.
Since there were very few children
who were full cyborgs at the time,
it must have been unimaginably difficult for him.
Still, when he thought about how the girl
must've borne the same difficulties,
he overcame his with ease.
And... was that girl ever found?
A girl who was in a plane crash and became a full cyborg...
That alone should've been a good enough lead,
but he could not find her.
Then, where did he find the girl's cybernetic body...?
When the boy was at a university lab,
he found it being preserved there as a specimen.
The boy knew right away that the
body was the girl he was looking for,
but he was ultimately unable to find the girl herself,
who had since moved on to a different body.
So the memories of that girl are still empty.
Where is the boy... right now?
Towards the end of the World War,
he was dispatched overseas.
He hasn't come back here since then, so...
he may have died.
I see...
Thank you for telling me the story.
I'm sure that the girl is also still looking
for the first boy she liked, even now.
The first boy she liked...?
The ice in your iced tea has all melted.
I know.
What is it?
Well, about that bunch's testing...
I want to let them try again after
rethinking the difficulty setting.
What do you think?
Where's this coming from?
Well, you see,
I remembered how I used to get
yelled at by my instructor,
back when I first joined, because I couldn't
really be at my full potential either...
That's true.
Maybe no one can do that
well from the very beginning.
Yeah...
It helps that you say that, too.
Finding out a galaxy
of planets and stars within me.
Listening to each of them
singing the same silent melody.
I've never seen such beauty
in possibility...
No smack of doubt or fear.
(Wake up)
I hear a voice.
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
I see inside
(the time is right)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
All I need,
to make all this reality.
(it's inside)
The beauty within the shell.
(deep within the shell)
(within the shell)
(Wake up)
I hear a voice
(And show the light)
hear a voice calling out to me.
(Wake up)
(the time is now)
hear a voice calling out to me.
I see inside,
(the time is now)
see the light now ever holding me.
All the truth,
(All the truth)
all I need,
to make all this reality,
it's inside
right here within the shell.